You know the myth... Now meet the legend.
Hickok is a western film directed by Timothy Woodward Jr..
Legendary Lawman and Gunslinger Wild Bill Hickok, is tasked with taming the wildest cow-town in the West, while delivering his own
brand of frontier Justice and infamous gunfighter's reputation as the fastest draw in the West is put to the test
Wild Bill Hickok, played by Luke Hemsworth.
Phil Poe, played by Trace Adkins.
Doc Rivers O'Roark, played by Bruce Dern.
Mattie, played by Cameron Richardson.
John Wesley Hardin, played by Kaiwi Lyman.
George Knox, played by Kris Kristofferson.
Hickok is a 2017 American Western film starring Luke Hemsworth,
Trace Adkins, Kris Kristofferson and Bruce Dern.
It was released in a limited theatrical engagement as well as
on video-on-demand by Cinedigm on July 7, 2017.